

Santo Domingo, Ecuador +593 (98) 2345–160

Hire-Me@FullStackWebDeveloper.xyz

FullStackWebDeveloper.xyz

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marantbq/



Full Stack Web Developer with more than 5 years of experience. Programming, E-commerce, and DirectAdmin Content creator for both YouTube and Udemy for about 4 years with creative video editing skills, cooperative team member willing to learn, share, and fulfill assignments and goals on time.

Problem-solving by bringing to life ideas through professional **Web Design and Development**. Always ready for a new challenge to change the world.

EDUCATION

Expected April 2024

B.S. in Web Design & Development
BYU-Idaho

December 2022

A.A.S. in Web Design & Development
BYU-Idaho

July 2022

Certificate in Web Development BYU-Idaho

July 2020

Certificate in Web Backend Development BYU-Idaho

SKILLS

Work

- HTML5 / EJS / Twig
- CSS3 / Sass
- JS / jQuery
- PHP
- SQL
- DirectAdmin
- · Git, Bitbucket, SSH
- PrestaShop, Drupal CMS
- REST API
- Python
- Jira

Language

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Fluent)



EXPERIENCE

November 2022 - Present

Full Stack Web Developer (Full Time)
Marbust Technology Company

- Developed Web Progressive Apps in Node.JS with Express, EJS, SQL, Sass, and JS.
- Created E-commerce Sites developed in PrestaShop working with Ecuador Payment Gateways.
- Produced Web Hosting, Programming and PrestaShop CMS videos for YouTube and Udemy.

April 2022 – November 2022

Front End Engineer (Full Time) Expandya

- Developed templates API, and CMS settings for Drupal with Symphony, Twig, JS, jQuery, and Sass.
- Worked collaboratively with Agile and Scrum methods by using Bitbucket as repositories tools through SSH console.

November 2021 - March 2022

Altura Designer's Suit Leader (Full Time) Altura S.A.

- Worked in Front-end apps with (HTML, Sass, JS, and jQuery).